https://www.eurosort.com/en/the-company/privacy-statement-eurosort-systems-b-v/

Contact
410-656-2101
Privacy Statement EuroSort Systems B.V.
PERSONAL DATA THAT WE PROCESS
EuroSort Systems B.V., having its registered office at the De Boomgaard 2 in (1243 HV) ‘s-Graveland, can process your personal data on account of the fact that you use the services of  EuroSort Systems B.V. and/or because you make these available to EuroSort Systems B.V. when filling in a contact form on the website. EuroSort Systems B.V. can process the following personal data:
Your given name and surnameYour (business) address detailsYour (business) telephone numberYour (business) email addressYour IP address
SPECIAL AND/OR SENSITIVE PERSONAL DATA THAT WE PROCESS
Our website and/or service are not meant to collect data about website visitors aged 16 or under, unless they have consent of a parent or guardian. We can, however, not check if a visitor is over 16. We therefore recommend parents to be involved in the online activities of their children in order to thus avoid that data are collected about children without parental consent. If you are convinced that we collected personal data about a minor without the said consent then contact us via info@distrisort.com and we shall delete the said data.
WITH WHAT PURPOSE AND ON THE BASIS OF WHAT FOUNDATION DO WE PROCESS PERSONAL DATAEuroSort Systems B.V. processes your personal data for the following purposes:
to contact you by telephone if so requested and/or to approach you in writing (by email and/or by post) if you can unexpectedly not be reached by telephone;to send our newsletter and/or information about sorting;to send invitations for trade fairs;to inform you of changes in our services and products.
In addition, EuroSort Systems B.V. can use your personal data within the framework of the implementation of an agreement for the provision of services concluded with you, usually comprising legal services.HOW LONG DOES EUROSORT SYSTEMS B.V. RETAIN DATAEuroSort Systems B.V. does not retain your personal data any longer than strictly required for the realisation of the purposes for which your data are collected. We apply the following retention periods for the following (categories of) personal data:Name, job title and business email address as long as relevant for the supply of information or the realisation of a project, as long as the relevant person is employed at the company.SHARING PERSONAL DATA WITH THIRD PARTIESEuroSort Systems B.V. only discloses your personal data to third parties if this is required for the implementation of an agreement with you or for compliance with a statutory duty.
INSPECTING, CORRECTING OR ERASING DATAYou are entitled to inspect your personal data or to have them corrected or erased. In addition, you are entitled to revoke your potential consent to the data processing or to object to the processing of your personal data by EuroSort Systems B.V. and you are entitled to data portability. You can send a request for information, correction or erasure to info@eurosort.com. EuroSort Systems B.V. shall react to your request as soon as possible, however within four weeks.
To ensure that the request for information was sent by you, we ask you to send a copy of your identity document with the request. Blacken out your passport photo, MRZ (machine readable zone, the bar with numbers at the bottom of the passport), passport number and civil service number on this copy. The latter to protect your privacy.
EuroSort Systems B.V. would also like to bring to your attention that you have the possibility of submitting a complaint to the national supervisory authority, the Data Protection Authority. This can be done via the following link: https://autoriteitpersoonsgegevens.nl/nl/contact-met-de-autoriteit-persoonsgegevens/tip-ons
ANALYSING WEBSITE VISITSGeneral visit data, including the IP address of your computer and the time of retrieval and data sent by your browser, are tracked on the website of EuroSort Systems B.V. These data are used for analyses of visiting and clicking behaviour on the website. EuroSort Systems B.V. uses this information to improve the operation of the website. These data are anonymised as much as possible and are not disclosed to third parties.
GOOGLE ANALYTICSEuroSort Systems B.V. uses Google Analytics to track how users use the website and how effective the AdWords advertisements of EuroSort Systems B.V. on the Google search result pages are.
The thus obtained information is, including the address of your computer (IP address), transferred to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Read the privacy policy of Google for more information. You can also find the privacy policy of Google Analytics there.
Google uses this information to track how our website is being used, to make reports about the website available to EuroSort Systems B.V. and to offer its advertisers information about the effectiveness of their campaigns.
Google can disclose this information to third parties if Google is held to do so by law or to the extent that the said third parties process the information on behalf of Google. EuroSort Systems B.V. cannot control this.
EuroSort Systems B.V. did not give Google consent to use Analytics information obtained via EuroSort Systems B.V. for other Google services.
COOKIES, OR COMPARABLE TECHNIQUES, THAT WE USEEuroSort Systems B.V. only uses technical and functional cookies. And analytical cookies that do not prejudice your privacy. A cookie is a small text file that is stored on your computer, tablet or smartphone with the first visit to this website. The cookies that we use are necessary for the technical operation of the website and your user convenience. They ensure that the website operates properly and remember, for instance, your preferred settings. They also allow us to optimise our website. You can deactivate cookies by configuring your internet browser in such way that it no longer stores cookies. In addition, you can delete all the previously stored information via the settings of your browser.
SECURITYEuroSort Systems B.V. takes the protection of your data seriously and takes appropriate measures to avoid abuse, loss, unauthorised access, undesired disclosure and unauthorised changes.  If you are under the impression that your data are nonetheless not secured properly or if there are indications of abuse then contact us on +31(0) 88 88 77 425 or via info@eurosort.com.
This website uses cookies.
Select ‘accept’ or read more about the Cookie Law AcceptDon't accept
